Hello everyone, this video will take you to quickly browse the new features and highlights of the Kolo 2025.0 version.
First is the main function
Now you can use our AI model pose generator to create all kinds of poses
Make the process of creating poses faster and easier
You can not only use the prompt system in the software
Quickly generate the pose you want
You can also combine text input to generate
You can also upload reference pictures to generate specific poses
After the pose is generated, you can save it to the computer
Then apply to other project files
In the new version, we optimized the version generator
In the current version, you can use it to create a T-shape
You only need to enter the size
The system will generate the corresponding paper
You can also manually adjust the parameters to the satisfaction effect
Click to create
The system will automatically complete the arrangement and sewing of the version
In addition, we can also use the AI version generator
You can enter the prompt to generate the model picture
Then create the corresponding version according to the model picture
Click to create
You can also try other prompt to create
Or upload the design pattern you designed to generate the version
The system will automatically generate the corresponding size version through built-in program calculation
You can adjust and modify on this basis
Click to create
The generated version will also automatically arrange and sew
We also optimized the function of the animation key frame in the new version
This can help you achieve quick animation editing
And provide more editing options to achieve accurate control
In the animation production process
You can edit and control various elements more freely
For example, gravity settings and other settings
And color editing, etc.
As shown here
This work is
New animation editor
Can help you create more exciting and lively animation works
In the new version, the hole is supported in the 3D window to check the hair effect
Can help you make quick judgments on the hair effect
New animation editor
No need to open the rendering window
Select the hair style material type
You can check the hair effect on the 3D window on the left side
New animation editor
As you can see, the rendering window can also be displayed simultaneously
The print and export function has also been fully upgraded
New animation editor
Now the software can choose to export according to the real application , and only export to the current material
Current material
New animation editor
and lock it in the current position to do the arrangement.
These improvements will unlock more application scenarios for collo-connection production.
Next, I will introduce the brightness function of the virtual model for you.
First of all, the AI model workshop increases the generation background options,
while improving the overall output effect of the image.
Let's generate a face first.
You can also upload a face picture.
Then we choose the background.
You can use the system prompt to generate a picture.
Then the background picture will be combined with the just-generated picture.
Or enter a specific text description to get the picture.
You can also upload a picture to rebuild the background or show the environment of the costume.
In addition, the new version has added the virtual model.
IK joint printing function
Improves the compatibility of the external virtual model model and the collo.
You only need to easily select the corresponding position at the 3D window.
Or use the automatic printing function.
You can apply all the posture materials in the collo.
The flip position is a simple and easy function to update and add this time.
You can flip any posture in the 3D window.
In the new version of the virtual model editor,
The shape adjustment of the hips and chest has been increased.
For the hips, you can control the curve shape on both sides.
And adjust the degree to which the hips are down or up.
For the chest, you can now select and add the scale size.
And apply different chest shapes through the switch option.
Next, we will introduce the relevant updates of the 3D window.
Our UV editor has been changed from the mode to the editor interface.
And in the main menu bar material UV tool bar download menu.
And now in the UV editor.
You can show the reverse and side of the texture.
All the覺 the paper busts can be
You can make my favorite student a man from the testis edward there.
Thank you guys for watching.
See you in the second part of the video if not here.
When you take a quick photo of the 3D window image, you can choose the color you want to save, save a single or multiple quick photos, and you can quickly export multiple color quick photos from the project file to display.
In the rendering window, you can now set the depth of each self-defined view. The method is very simple, use the left mouse button to determine the focal point.
Clue will automatically apply it to the corresponding self-defined view setting.
Let you experience the effect in Clue.
The effect is as controlled as in the actual photo.
Now I will introduce you to the optimization of the keypad function.
In Clue, you can use a false needle,
create multiple focal points for a keypad,
click on the keypad,
then click on the keypad in the place where you want to paste the clipboard to add a focal point.
With this new function,
you can easily create multiple focal points.
You can add multiple fixed positions to a keypad,
and achieve a more realistic keypad simulation.
Then there is the function update about the simulation.
New range drag tool
can help you control the area range and the strength of the effect when you open the simulation,
help you achieve faster and accurate clothing adjustments.
Next is the related updates regarding user interface.
Now when you open the project file,
you can choose whether to open and display it according to the display status when saving the file.
It is also possible to annotate the layout of the new clue.
Click on the new clue.
At the same time, you can add the previously collected files to the new drawing library and transfer them to the label page of the new drawing library, and rename it.
Then let's take a look at the function update related to the material.
Now you can directly switch the color by clicking on the color block in the object window, and you can use the shortcut key to open the color editor.
Now you can check and adjust the front and back or side colors of the fabric in the color editor.
Make it easier for everyone to use the color editor to edit the material color.
Next, I will introduce the optimization of the label function.
Now you can open the 2D window.
Set relevant settings to the label information of the version.
For example, the size, color and direction of the font.
Make the label information more clear.
Finally, let's take a look at the brightness function update about 2D CAD.
The optimization of the generated round and smooth curve tool, on the basis of the original usage method,
has added a new usage method to adjust the curve shape,
allowing you to achieve better control and editing of the curve,
and only adjust the selected curve separately,
without affecting the curve shape of other parts.
Achieve more free and accurate curve adjustment.
In addition, there are more new functions.
Welcome to the latest version of the
CLO.
Please keep following us.